<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Bethesda>
  <Descriptions>
    <Description Name="iNumThreads">Number of threads to use with the game. Edit at your own risk. No proof this actually does anything</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisablePlayerCollision">Probably some sort of No-Clip. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bSimpleLighting">Enables simple lighting. Will probably increase performance and lower lighting quality. Needs Testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunShadowUpdateTime">How long it takes shadows to move to their new position when the sun position updates. Lower = smoother transitions</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunUpdateThreshold">How often the Sun position updates. Lower = Faster</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableVolumetricLighting">Enables volumetric lighting. Probably costs a lot of CPU if this command still works. Would look great in VR though. Needs Testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fTAAPostSharpen">Increase/decrease the sharpening effect while using TAA</Description>    
    <Description Name="bDrawShadows">Enable or disables shadows. May increase performance. Probably looks bad</Description>
    <Description Name="bCharacterLighting">Enable or disable character lighting. Probably looks more realistic with it turned off. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bShadowsOnGrass">Toggles the ability of objects to cast shadows upon grass. The grass itself does not cast shadows. This may be disabled for a minor performance increase.</Description>
    <Description Name="bTreesReceiveShadows">Toggles the ability of trees to cast shadows on themselves. It may be disabled for a slight performance gain.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowShaderCache">Probably enables or disables the shader cache, if it works at all. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseSunBeams">Possibly related to God rays? Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fDecalLifetime">How long Decals remain in a game</Description>
    <Description Name="iVRWindowSize">Sets the size of the VR Window on your desktop. Not sure if this is a x or y value</Description>
    <Description Name="bDoRadialBlur">Enables or disables depth of field</Description>
    <Description Name="fVrScale">Scale of your player in VR. Higher makes you more of a giant (not just height but relative size). A lot of people set this to 75-76</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceImmortal">Probably gives you God mode when enabled? Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceGodMode">Another god mode command? See: bForceImmortal. Not sure if there is a difference</Description>
    <Description Name="fSneakEnterThreshold">The percentage of your height before considered sneaking. Lower = You have to crouch lower to activate. Setting to 0 probably makes it where you are never in sneak mode while crouching</Description>
    <Description Name="fSneakExitThreshold">The percentage of your height before your player leaves sneak mode. Higher = You have to stand higher to exit sneaking</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowVRCheating">Lets you lean into objects without being kicked back. Feels more immersive when turned on</Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugAlwaysShowWands">Setting to 1 always shows your controllers in game</Description>
    <Description Name="bVRPauseOnControllerDisconnect">Turn this off to prevent the game from pausing when one of your controllers turns off</Description>
    <Description Name="bPauseOnVROverlay">Disabling this will keep your game running while you open the vr overlay</Description>
    <Description Name="fGunRotation">Changes the rotation of your gun, a common request for people to fine tune the angle they hold the gun at. Try 60-65</Description>
    <Description Name="fSkyScaleFactor">Alters star field distance (users report 1000-2000 is a good distance)</Description>
    <Description Name="bBorderRegionsEnabled">Turn this off to be able to walk past the map invisible borders. Use with caution</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAllGore">Turn off gore, maybe good if you want kids to try this out or you don't like seeing blood</Description>
    <Description Name="bAlwaysActive">Disable this if you want the game to pause if another window is in front</Description>
    <Description Name="uGridsToLoad">Don't mess with this. It causes issues. It determines how many cells around your player to load. Will corrupt your save if you edit this midgame</Description>
    <Description Name="iNumHWThreads">How many threads the game uses. No real proof that editing this value does anything at all</Description>
    <Description Name="fComfortModeVignetteHardness">Change this value to make the vignette fade in more or less (lower = gradual fade to black)</Description>
    <Description Name="bFadeWorldWhenMenuIsOpen">Fade the game world when you open a menu, or leave it clear. Needs to be tested</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapVrDirectMovementSpeed">Probably how fast you can direct move in VR? Value is pretty height, might not even do anything. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fLockScale">Scale of the lock while lock picking. Make the value bigger to make the lock bigger</Description>
    <Description Name="fLockPositionZ">Z location of the lock while picking</Description>
    <Description Name="fLockPositionY">Y location of the lock while picking</Description>
    <Description Name="fLockPositionX">X Position of the lock while picking</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDCompassScale">Size of the compass. Heigher number = bigger compass</Description>
    <Description Name="sHUDCompassModel">Perhaps you can edit this with a custom compass model when a mod is released</Description>
    <Description Name="fNoteScale">Probably changes the size of notes when being read. If this works it could make it easier to read in VR. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fBookScale">Probably changes the size of books when being read. If this works it could make it easier to read in VR. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bPlayVRMeleeWorldImpactSounds">Probably enabling this lets you hear the sound of melee impacts when you hit world objects</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseBulletWaterDisplacements">Probably shows bullets splashing in water. If turning this off works it could potentially increase performance. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceHighDetailReflections">In Fallout 3, this forced more objects to be reflected in the water. Doesn't appear to be used by this game</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceLowDetailReflections">In Fallout 3, this forced less objects to be reflected in the water. Doesn't appear to be used by this game</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWater">Stops water from rendering. Water still is there and you can swim in it</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowTutorials">Enable or Disable Tutorials. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowCrosshair">Show or hide the crosshair. Not sure if this effects VR or not</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWandDirectionalMovement">Turning this off makes you no longer steer your character using your hands</Description>
    <Description Name="iConsoleTextSize">Text size of the developer console</Description>
    <Description Name="rConsoleTextColor">RGB Value to change the color of the developer console text</Description>
    <Description Name="iConsoleSizeScreenPercent">How much of the screen the developer console takes up (Percentage)</Description>
    <Description Name="iAutoSaveCount">How many autosaves before overwrite</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAutoSave">Enables or disables autosaving. (0 = enabled)</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableAudio">Set to 0 to disable audio. Probably not useful for anyone.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceNPCsUseAmmo">This will force the NPC to use ammo on all guns. 1 = Forced 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceFullDetail">Force full details of trees. May make the game look prettier at the cost of performance</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableTrees">Toggles the "dynamic" rendering of trees. If disabled, all trees will be skinned and inanimate, using the "static" version of tree rendering, which also removes tree popping.</Description>
    <Description Name="bFogEnabled">>Enable or Disable the Fog weather Effect. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled. Could potentially increase performance if disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bPrecipitation">Enable or Disable Rain Weather Effect. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bBloodSplatterEnabled">Enables or disables blood splatter on the screen. Might not do anything in VR. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="uDecalCount">Total number of decals allowed at once. Could effect performance</Description>
    <Description Name="uLightCount">Number of real lights allowed at once. Could effect performance</Description>
    <Description Name="iShadowMapResolution">Shadow resolution. Edit in proper intervals (256, 512, 1024, etc)</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseTAA">Use TAA post processing. Disabling may increase aliasing but makes the game less fuzzy looking</Description>
    <Description Name="bFXAAEnabled">Enables FXAA antialiasing</Description>
    <Description Name="bGamepadEnabled">disable this to disable the use of a gamepad for this game</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDOpacity">Transparency of the HUD. 1 = Fully Opaque. 0 = Fully Transparent (Invisible)</Description>
    <Description Name="bSaveOnPause">Enable to autosave when the game is paused</Description>
    <Description Name="bSaveOnTravel">Enable to autosave when you fast travel</Description>
    <Description Name="bSaveOnWait">Enable to autosave when you wait</Description>
    <Description Name="bSaveOnRest">Enable to autosave when you sleep</Description>    
    <Description Name="bShowCompass">Show or Hide the Compass from your UI. 1 = Shown 0 = Hidden</Description>
    <Description Name="bLeftHandedMode">Set to 1 to make your character left handed</Description>
    <Description Name="bDirectMovementWithWands">Set to 1 to use direct movement instead of teleport</Description>    
    <Description Name="bShowQuestMarkers">Show or hide quest markers. Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="iDifficulty">Difficulty of the game. 0 = Easiest -> 5 = Hardest</Description>
    <Description Name="bComfortSwim">Enables or disables comfort swimming (motion sickness prevention)</Description>
    <Description Name="bOneTimeCalibrationCompleted">Set to 0 if you want to go through the calibration/tutorial again before starting the game</Description>
    <Description Name="bComfortSneak">Enables or disables the comfort vignette while sneaking</Description>
    <Description Name="bRealisticShield">Not sure what this does to shields, but probably like the bow, probably gives you more control over the shield</Description>
    <Description Name="bAlwaysRunByDefault">Set to 1 to always run when pressing forward. Needs testing in VR</Description>
    <Description Name="bGamePadRumble">Enable or disables the rumblepad in your controllers</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseRealisticBowAiming">Set to 1 to let you control your bow and arrow more. A lot better than the default bow handling</Description>
    <Description Name="fAutosaveEveryXMins">How many minutes between autosaves</Description>
    <Description Name="bComfortModeWhileMoving">Enables or disables the comfort vignette when moving around</Description>
    <Description Name="bComfortModeWhileTurning">Enables or disables the comfort vignette when turning</Description>
    <Description Name="bDecals">Enables or disables decals. Turning off could increase performance</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxSkinDecals">How many decals on character skins. Lower could increase performance</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxDecals">Global number of decals that can render at once. Lower could increase performance</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDMenuX">Moves the compass and healthbars across the X axis</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDMenuY">Moves the compass and healthbars across the Y axis</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDMenuZ">Moves the compass and healthbars across the Z axis</Description>
    <Description Name="bHealthBarShowing">Show the Enemy Health Bar. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled. Doesn't have any effect in VR so far. Needs more testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunBaseSize">Sets the sun's base size. Setting it to 0 will remove the sun altogether, albeit the day will still be lit.</Description>
    <Description Name="iCompassPosition">Decides where the compass is located, you can toggle this in the in-game VR Settings. 1 = Above your view, 0 = Below your view</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxTime">Physics refresh rate. Recommended to change to 0.0111. Recommended to change fMaxTimeComplex relative to this value.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxTimeComplex">Complex Physics refresh rate. Recommended to set this to double the value of fMaxTime</Description>
    <Description Name="bDoDepthOfField">Setting to 0 disables UNDERWATER FOG (NOT Depth of field unfortunately)</Description>
    <Description Name="fMeleeSwingAngularVelocityThreshold">Sets the sensitivity of a registered swing of a weapon using motion controllers. This is for the primary hand. See 'fShieldLinearVelocityThreshold' for non-primary</Description>
    <Description Name="fShieldLinearVelocityThreshold">Recommend setting to 2-4.5. Sets the sensitivity of a registered swing/block of a shield/weapon using motion controllers. This is for your non-primary hand. See 'fMeleeSwingAngularVelocityThreshold' for primary</Description>
    <Description Name="fMeleeLinearVelocityThreshold">Recommend setting to 4-6. Sets the sensitivity of a registered melee punch</Description>
    <Description Name="bFull Screen">Set this to 1 to make your desktop window full screen. This may increase performance due to how Windows treats fullscreen games vs windowed/borderless</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxNumPhysicsStepsPerUpdate">Set this to 1 to get rid of hiccuping objects</Description>
    <Description Name="iShadowUpdateFrameDelay">Set this to 1 to make the shadows stop flickering on 3d movable objects after you edit fMaxTime</Description>
    <Description Name="fNearDistance">How close an object needs to be to your view before it dissapears. Setting to a low value like 13 may help with mountains flickering</Description>
    <Description Name="fMagicRotationPitch">Sets the angle from your hands that magic projects from. Set to 40-60 depending on where you want it (higher = higher in the hand)</Description>
    <Description Name="fMagicHandRotate">Rotates the hand model when you are casting magic</Description>
    <Description Name="fLeftHandShieldRotationRoll">Set to -10 to make it easier to move and block with your shield at the same time</Description>
    <Description Name="fRightHandShieldRotationRoll">Set to 10 to make it easier to move and block with your shield at the same time</Description>
    <Description Name="fActivatePickLength">How close you have to be to an object to grab it. 20 is more immersive</Description>
    <Description Name="fAutoAimScreenPercentageVROverride">Set to 0 to turn off the Bow auto aim. Also see 'fAutoAimScreenPercentageVR'</Description>
    <Description Name="fAutoAimScreenPercentageVR">Set to 0 to turn off the Bow auto aim. Also see 'fAutoAimScreenPercentageVROverride'</Description>
    <Description Name="bImmediatelyGrabObjectOnActivate">Set this to 0 to remove the pull to character effect when you pick up items.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal0">Volume Control: Fallout(Voice) Skyrim(Effects)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal1">Volume Control: Fallout(Music) Skyrim(Footsteps)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal2">Volume Control: Fallout(Effects) Skyrim(Voice)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal3">Volume Control: Fallout(Footsteps) Skyrim(Music)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal4">Volume Control: Fallout(Radio) Skyrim(Unknown?)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal5">Volume Control: Fallout(Unassigned) Skyrim(Unassigned)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal6">Volume Control: Fallout(Unassigned) Skyrim(Unassigned)</Description>
    <Description Name="fVal7">Volume Control: Fallout(Unassigned) Skyrim(Unassigned)</Description>
    <Description Name="fDualCastMinDistance">How far apart your hands must be to dual cast magic. Recommend to set to 20 for a more immersive experience</Description>
    <Description Name="fMinPulsesForFullSwipe">changes how many menu items are selected for one swipe across the track pad (minimum)</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxPulsesForFullSwipe">changes how many menu items are selected for one swipe across the track pad (maximum)</Description>
    <Description Name="fAlternateTriggerThreshold">If you prefer a hair trigger that you cant keep mashing while its still depressed, set to 0.001</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseAlternateTriggerThreshold">Set to 0 to bypass the alternate trigger threshold (search: fAlternateTriggerThreshold)</Description>
    <Description Name="fDownwardGrabFloorDistanceMultiplier">Setting this to 0 stops the wands from extending out when the controller is pointed down</Description>
    <Description Name="fSecondaryWandMaxGrabDistance">this is ignored by fDownwardGrabFloorDistanceMultiplier when aiming at the floor</Description>
    <Description Name="fPrimaryWandMaxGrabDistance">this is ignored by fDownwardGrabFloorDistanceMultiplier when aiming at the floor</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableCompositor">This stops the game from rendering in the headset. You'll just see the steamVR loading screen. Pretty useless for us</Description>
    <Description Name="fVrPowerArmorScaleMultiplier">Scale of your player inside Power Armor. This is a multiplier to fVrScale so only change this if you want to be a lot bigger in Power Armor but not out</Description>
    <Description Name="bVrShowIntroBink">Disables the VR intro Video when starting the game</Description>
    <Description Name="bAutoLoadLastSaveGame">Setting to 1 will just load the last save game instead of asking you to pick a save</Description>
    <Description Name="fComfortVignetteSizeMax">This effects the maximum value for the Vignette when using the in-game slider</Description>
    <Description Name="fComfortVignetteSizeMin">This effects the minimum value for the Vignette when using the in-game slider</Description>
    <Description Name="bInfiniteAmmo">Probably for giving infinite ammo, but I wasn't able to get it to work when set to 1</Description>
    <Description Name="fVrRunSpeedScalar">Increasing this will increase how fast your character will sprint. May cause vomiting if used incorrectly</Description>
    <Description Name="fVrStrafeSpeedScalar">Increasing this will increase how fast your character will straf. May cause vomiting if used incorrectly</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAllSaves">Disables game saving when set to 1</Description>
    <Description Name="fWorkbenchScale">Sets distance AND scale of the floating crafting menu. Don't set it too high as the menu gets hidden by walls/furniture.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPrimaryWandHUDZ">Moves the HUD (ie ammo in your gun) on your primary wand hand on the Z axis in the world (Height Up and down)</Description>
    <Description Name="fPrimaryWandHUDY">Moves the HUD (ie ammo in your gun) on your primary wand hand on the Y axis in the world (depth back/forward)</Description>
    <Description Name="fPrimaryWandHUDX">Moves the HUD (ie ammo in your gun) on your primary wand hand on the X axis in the world (left to right)</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDLootZ">Changes the location of the Quick Loot HUD on the Z plane in the world (up/down height from your wand)</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDLootY">Changes the location of the Quick Loot HUD on the Y plane in the world (depth from your wand)</Description>
    <Description Name="fHUDLootX">Changes the location of the Quick Loot HUD on the X plane in the world (left to right of your wand)</Description>
    <Description Name="fFavoritesTouchpadCenterButtonPercent">Sets the proportion (not percent) of the trackpad where a press is considered a center-button press and not a directional press up down left or right.</Description>
    <Description Name="bInvalidateOlderFiles">Set this to 1 to allow the loading of loose files in the data\ folder</Description>
    <Description Name="sResourceDataDirsFinal">This can be used to support loading loose folders in the Data directory. This method has been superceeded with bInvalidateOlderFiles</Description>
    <Description Name="bFootstepSoundsEnabled">Enables or Disables Footstep sounds. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultMasterVolume">Master Volume Level. Can be 'boosted' by setting higher than 1</Description>
    <Description Name="bApplyCameraNodeAnimations">You need to set this to 0 if you are trying to mess with the default camera location for third person.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAutoVanityMode">Disables Vanity mode. 1 = Disable 0 = Enable</Description>
    <Description Name="f1st3rdSwitchDelay">How long of a delay between switching from 1st to 3rd person. Lower is faster.</Description>
    <Description Name="f3rdPersonAimFOV">The ADS field of view when in Third person.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseWheelZoomIncrement">How much further/closer you move to your player while using the scrollwheel in third person. Lower = Smoother transitions</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseWheelZoomSpeed">How fast zooming occurs when scrolling the mouse to change your distance to your player in third person</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderCombatAddY">Moves the Y axis of the third person Camera while in combat</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderCombatPosX">Moves the X axis of the third person Camera while in combat</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderCombatPosZ">Moves the Z axis of the third person Camera while in combat</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderMeleeCombatPosX">Moves the X axis of the camera while in melee</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderMeleeCombatPosZ">Moves the Z axis of the camera while in melee</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderPosX">Moves the X axis of the third person Camera while not in combat</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderPosZ">Moves the Z axis of the third person Camera while not in combat</Description>
    <Description Name="fVanityModeMaxDist">The furthest distance you can zoom out in in vanity mode.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVanityModeMinDist">The closest vanity mode can get to your model</Description>
    <Description Name="bIronSightsZoomEnable">Enables or Disables Iron sights zooming. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled. This hasn't been tested</Description>
    <Description Name="fAimDownDegrees">How many degrees Vertically can you aim. 90 = Directly down.</Description>
    <Description Name="fAimUpDegrees">How many degrees Vertically can you aim. 90 = Directly above.</Description>
    <Description Name="bBackgroundMouse">Enable this to show the windows Cursor while playing. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fEnterWorkshopDelay">How long you have to hold the workshop key to Enter workshop mode</Description>
    <Description Name="fIronSightsPitchSpeedRatio">This alters the speed of your mouse while in Iron sights. Set to 1 to disable speed difference.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseHeadingXScale">Mouse X Axis sensitivity multiplier. Higher makes the mouse move faster Left to Right</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseHeadingYScale">Mouse Y Axis sensitivity multiplier. Higher makes the mouse move faster Up to Down</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyLightDelay">Sets how long you have to hold the pipboy key to turn on your flashlight</Description>
    <Description Name="fPitchSpeedRatio">This is the multiplier that controls Up and down (Y axis) mouse movement. Setting this to 1 will make the sensitivity ratio equal to your X axis</Description>
    <Description Name="fPowerArmorExitDelay">How long you must hold the Exit power armor key to trigger</Description>
    <Description Name="fThrowDelay">How long you have to hold the bash key to pull the pin of a grenade</Description>
    <Description Name="fZKeyDelay">Sets how long you have to hold the use key to pick up an object</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxSkinDecalPerActor">Set this higher for more decals, could effect performance</Description>    
    <Description Name="bShowMarkers">This will Show or Hide Markers. 1 = Show 0 = Hide</Description>
    <Description Name="fDecalLOD0">How far away from the player decals show</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefault1stPersonFOV">The Field of view for the Firstperson camera</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultFOV">This edits the first person FOV. Don't mess with this in VR</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultWorldFOV">The Field of view for the third person camera. Set to 80-100 for a better PC experience</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyScreenDiffuseIntensity">Changes the Brightness of the Pipboy Text/Images</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyScreenDiffuseIntensityPA">Changes the Brightness of the Pipboy Text/Images while in Power Armor</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyScreenEmitIntensity">Changes the Brightness of the Pipboy Text/Images</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyScreenEmitIntensityPA">Changes the Brightness of the Pipboy Text/Images while in Power Armor</Description>
    <Description Name="iLocation X">X location for your Game window to appear at. 0 sets it on the default monitor.</Description>
    <Description Name="iLocation Y">Y location for your Game window to appear at. 0 sets it on the default monitor.</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPipboyLightR">Red color channel for Pipboy Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPipboyLightG">Green color channel for Pipboy Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPipboyLightB">Blue color channel for Pipboy Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorR">Red color channel for Power Armor UI (Dont think it works though) 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorG">Green color channel for Power Armor UI (Dont think it works though) 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorB">Blue color channel for Power Armor UI (Dont think it works though) 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorLightR">Red color channel for Power Armor Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorLightG">Green color channel for Power Armor Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="uiPowerArmorLightB">Blue color channel for Power Armor Light 0->255</Description>
    <Description Name="bEssentialTakeNoDamage">This lets you kill Essential NPCs. Setting this to 0 can break the game if main quest characters Die!</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerHealthSaveOnPauseLimit">How much health you must have for the game to perform an autosave. 1 = Full health 0 = no health.</Description>
    <Description Name="iTerminalLockoutTime">How long you are locked out of a terminal if you fail to hack it. (In Seconds)</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableMainMenuBink">This Enables or Disables the video on the Main menu. Disabling may make your main menu load faster on slower systems.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceUpdateDiffuseOnly">You must set this to 0 If you mess with the Degrade and Upgrade Texture Distance settings</Description>
    <Description Name="bPauseOnAltTab">Set this to 0 to keep the game from pausing when you alt tab</Description>
    <Description Name="bPlayMainMenuMusic">Set this to 0 to turn off the main menu music</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseHardDriveCache">Set this to 1 if you don't have enough RAM to keep the game loaded. Could help with performance on weak systems.</Description>
    <Description Name="fEncumberedReminderTimer">How often the game reminds you that you are carrying too much. Lower = More reminders</Description>
    <Description Name="iTextureDegradeDistance0">The First Tier distance from your player that texture quality degrades (Helps with performance)</Description>
    <Description Name="iTextureDegradeDistance1">The Second Tier distance from your player that texture quality degrades (Helps with performance)</Description>
    <Description Name="iTextureUpgradeDistance0">The first Tier distance from your player that texture quality Increases</Description>
    <Description Name="iTextureUpgradeDistance1">The Second Tier distance from your player that texture quality increases</Description>
    <Description Name="sIntroMovie">Use this to specify an Intro Movie File</Description>
    <Description Name="sIntroSequence">Sequence of Intro Videos to play. Set this the value 'none' to disable.</Description>
    <Description Name="sLanguage">Game Language</Description>
    <Description Name="sMainMenuMusic">This selects the music file to play on the main menu</Description>
    <Description Name="sMenuFocusSoundFile">Focus Sound Effect file</Description>
    <Description Name="sMenuCancelSoundFile">Cancel Sound Effect file</Description>
    <Description Name="sMenuNewGameSoundFile">New Game Sound Effect file</Description>
    <Description Name="sMenuOKSoundFile">'OK' Sound Effect file</Description>
    <Description Name="sStartingConsoleCommand">Console Command to execute When the game starts</Description>
    <Description Name="uExterior Cell Buffer">Outside Cell buffer size. Game doesn't read any value lower than 47 for some reason. Increase this if yo u increase your uGridsToLoad.</Description>
    <Description Name="uMainMenuDelayBeforeAllowSkip">Delay at the main menu before input lets you skip the video. Set to 1 to make it instant. 0 does not work.</Description>
    <Description Name="iMinGrassSize">Lower Equals higher Grass Density. May decrease performance. Put higher to lower Grass Density</Description>
    <Description Name="fBookOpenTime">How long it takes a book to open. Not sure if lower = Faster</Description>
    <Description Name="fCrosshairAlphaPercent">The transparency of the Crosshair. 0% is completely transparent. 100% is completely opaque.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxSubtitleDistance">How far you can get from an NPC before the subtitles dissapear</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneX">Margin from the edge of the screen (x axis on 4:3) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneXWide">Margin from the edge of the screen (x axis on 16:9) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneXWide16x10">Margin from the edge of the screen (x axis on 16:10) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneY">Margin from the edge of the screen (y axis on 4:3) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneYWide">Margin from the edge of the screen (y axis on 16:9) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="fSafeZoneYWide16x10">Margin from the edge of the screen (y axis on 16:10) your UI is placed. Lower = Closer</Description>
    <Description Name="uConfirmContainerTakeAllMinimumItems">How many of the same items must be in a container before it asks you to confirm if you want them all</Description>
    <Description Name="uSubtitleB">Blue Color Channel for Subtitle text. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="uSubtitleG">Green Color Channel for Subtitle text. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="uSubtitleR">Red Color Channel for Subtitle text. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="iPipboyColorB">Blue Channel color of the Pipboy. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="iPipboyColorG">Green Channel color of the Pipboy. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="iPipboyColorR">Red Channel color of the Pipboy. 0-255</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowYesToAll">Lets you select Yes for All if prompted by multiple prompts. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bBlockMessageBoxes">Blocks or Allows Message Boxes. 1 = Blocked 0 = Allow</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseCompanionWarping">Set this to 0 to stop Companions from Warping to you when they are too far away. 1 = Enable Warping 0 = Disable</Description>
    <Description Name="bPipboyDisableFX">Disables all Pipboy Effects. Useful if a mod reskins the pipboy UI. 1 = Disabled FX 0 = Enabled FX</Description>
    <Description Name="bPipboyEffectColorOnLight">Set this to 0 to not use the pipboy screen color as your flashlight color.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangedLongDistance">How far away an enemy can be for VATS to work. Higher = Further distances</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectSky">Reflect the sky in the water. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterHiRes">Use High Resolution water. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunGlareSize">Changes the size of the glare of the sun. Higher = Bigger</Description>
    <Description Name="bInfiniteItems">Possibly will give you infinite Items in workshop mode? Untested. 1 = Enabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bWorkshopAutoSaveOnExit">Should the game auto save when you exist Work Shop Mode? 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bWorkshopEnableGridBasedSnapping">Enable Grid snapping for workshop items. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fItemHoldDistantSpeed">How far away an item can be for you to be able to hold it (Higher = Further)</Description>
    <Description Name="fItemRotationSpeed">How fast you can rotate an item (higher = faster)</Description>
    <Description Name="bInvertYValues">Invert the Gamepad Y Axis. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fGamepadHeadingSensitivity">Gamepad sensitivity. Higher = Faster</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseHeadingSensitivity">Mouse Sensitivity. Higher = Faster</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowShadowcasterNPCLights">Enable this to allow NPC lights to cast shadows. ( Will lower performance) 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bBorderless">Enabled Borderless Mode. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableWetnessMaterials">Enables or disables wetness materials. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceIgnoreSmoothness">This is a texture setting, not mouse acceleration. Not sure if it really changes much</Description>
    <Description Name="bMaximizeWindow">Stretches the window to fit your resolution. (May cause the game to be cut off) 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bSAOEnable">Enables or Disables Ambient Occlusion. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bTopMostWindow">Sets the game to always be on top of all windows. This will prevent you from being able to alt tab on single monitors.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVolumetricLightingEnable">Enable or disbale the Volumetric Lighting (May increase performance) 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fBlendSplitDirShadow">This is the radius of how far shadows will start to decrease in quality (LOD) Lower will decrease performance</Description>
    <Description Name="fDirShadowDistance">How far to render shadows. Lower = Better performance</Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowDistance">How far away shadows should render. Higher will decrease performance</Description>
    <Description Name="iMaxAnisotropy">Sets Anistropic Filtering. 0 2 4 8 16 are the values you should use</Description>
    <Description Name="iMaxDecalsPerFrame">Total number of decals to render every frame</Description>
    <Description Name="iPresentInterval">This enables or disables Vsync in game. 0 = off 1=on. Some Report 2 works as well.</Description>    
    <Description Name="iSize H">Height (Y) Resolution Value.</Description>
    <Description Name="iSize W">Width (X) Resolution Value.</Description>
    <Description Name="iVolumetricLightingQuality">Volumetric Lighting Quality. 0 = Lowest -> 3 = Highest</Description>
    <Description Name="sAntiAliasing">Set the AA to use for the game. FXAA or TAA</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowFloatingQuestMarkers">Shows or hides Floating quest markers on the compass. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bPipboyCompanionEnabled">Enables or disables the Pipboycompanion App. 1 = Enable 0 = Disable</Description>
    <Description Name="fGrassStartFadeDistance">This determines how far away from your character you can see grass.</Description>
    <Description Name="bLensFlare">Enable or Disable Lens Flare effect. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bMBEnable">Enable or Disable Motion Blur Effect. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bScreenSpaceBokeh">Enable or Disable Bokeh (High quality motion Blur) 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bDialogueCameraEnable">Enable or disable the use of the dialogue camera. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bDialogueSubtitles">Enable or Disable Dialogue Subtitles. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bGeneralSubtitles">Enable or Disable General Subtitles. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="iHUDColorR">Red Color Channel for the Heads up Display</Description>
    <Description Name="iHUDColorG">Green Color Channel for the Heads up Display</Description>
    <Description Name="iHUDColorB">Blue Color Channel for the Heads up Display</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableFileSelection">Set this to 1 to enable plugin support in the launcher (may no longer work) 1 = Enable 2 = Disable</Description>
    <Description Name="bScreenSpaceReflections">Enable or disable Screenspace Reflections. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bScreenSpaceSubsurfaceScattering">Enable or Disable Screenspace Subsurface Scattering. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODFadeOutMultActors">Fadeout value for Actors. Higher = Further distance</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODFadeOutMultItems">Fadeout value for Items. Higher = Further distance</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODFadeOutMultObjects">Fadeout value for Objects. Higher = Further distance</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODFadeOutMultSkyCell">Fadeout value for Sky cells. Higher = Further distance</Description>
    <Description Name="bCrosshairEnabled">Enable or disable the crosshair. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="iMaxDesired">Max Particles to render</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyEffectColorR">Pipboy Red Color Channel Value (0-1.0)</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyEffectColorG">Pipboy Green Color Channel Value (0-1.0)</Description>
    <Description Name="fPipboyEffectColorB">Pipboy Blue Color Channel Value (0-1.0)</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectColorR">Red Color Channel for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectColorG">Green Color Channel for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectColorB">Blue Color Channel for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightColorR">Highlight - Red Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightColorG">Highlight - Green Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightColorB">Highlight - Blue Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightPAColorR">Power Armor Highlight - Red Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightPAColorG">Power Armor Highlight - Green Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="fModMenuEffectHighlightPAColorB">Power Armor Highlight - Blue Channel Color for the Weapon/Armor Modding UI</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterDepth">Enable or Disable Water Depth. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterReflections">Enables or disables Water Reflections. May help performance on weaker systems. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderMeleeCombatAddY">Moves the Y axis of the camera while in melee</Description>
    <Description Name="fPitchZoomOutMaxDist">How far you can zoom out while in third person.</Description>
    <Description Name="iDefaultWaitHours">Default Hours value when you press the Wait button.</Description>
    <Description Name="bNVFlexEnable">Enables NVFlex. 1 = Enabled 0 = Disabled</Description>
    <Description Name="bNvGodraysEnable">Turns on/off the God Rays (Nvidia Tech). Might be depreciated (at least in FO4VR)</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableRainOcclusion">Turns on/off the Rain Occlusion. Might be depreciated (at least in FO4VR)</Description>
    <Description Name="iTexMipMapSkip">Changing may help with LOD texture pop-in...Might be depreciated (at least in FO4VR)</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableVatsWithScopes">Set to 1 to allow you to use scopes while also using VATS</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableRoomscaleMovement">Set to 1 to let your hitbox move along with your real movements around your playspace. Turn off to go back to a static hitbox</Description>
    <Description Name="fRoomscaleMovementGradualRealignSpeed">Probably how fast your hitbox updates to your movements... Needs testing</Description>
    <Description Name="fArrowSnapDistance">Lowering this prevents the autonocking of arrows at further distances. Set to 0 to turn off, recommend setting to 1</Description>
    <Description Name="fArrowLerpDistance">Lowering this prevents the autonocking of arrows at further distances. Set to 0 to turn off, recommend setting to 1.5</Description>
    <Description Name="fBowHoldOffsetY">Changings the grip position on the bow. Recommend changing to -6.6</Description>
    <Description Name="fActivateRolloverWandScale">Change the size of activation text. Lower = Smaller</Description>
    <Description Name="bAlwaysShowHands">Shows or hides your vr hands on weapons</Description>
    <Description Name="bRenderSkinnedTrees">Disables "Skinned trees" when set to 0. Basically lowers tree quality. May increase performance</Description>
    <Description Name="fTreeLoadDistance">How far trees render in. Setting this to 100000 has a low performance cost and a huge visual upgrade</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableAutoDynamicResolution">Set to 0 to turn of the automatica adjustment of in game super sampling (highly recommended)</Description>
    <Description Name="fRenderTargetSizeMultiplier">In Game super sampling. 1.0 is no super sampling. This is a multiplier.</Description>
    <Description Name="bShouldDisableDMInVATS">Disable Direct Movement while VATS is active. Disable=1 Enable DM=0</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSFireWeaponActionPointsMultiplier">VATS cost multiplier per weapon fire</Description>
    <Description Name="fUHmdRotationLagMaxDistance">The farthest away UI elements will get before following the headset</Description>
    <Description Name="fUHmdRotationLagMinDistance">The minimum distance UI elements need to be before they will start timing for fUHmdRotationLagDuration to eventually be moved back into view</Description>
    <Description Name="fUHmdRotationLagDuration">How long UI elements need to be outside of fUHmdRotationLagMinDistance before they move back into view</Description>
    <Description Name="fUHmdRotationLagRecoveryAcceleration">How quickly UI elements accelerate to their fUHmdRotationLagRecoveryMaxSpeed</Description>
    <Description Name="fUHmdRotationLagRecoveryMaxSpeed">How quickly UI elements move back into view</Description>      
    <Description Name="bAllowCreateGrass">Turns on/off grass in the game. 0 = off 1 = on</Description>
    <Description Name="bAutoWaterSilhouetteReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed. This setting originates with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectLODLand">This toggles land reflections in the water. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAlwaysSaveAllInfo">This was added with the official 1.2 patch. This default value was changed from 0 (disabled) to 1 (enabled) with the official 1.3 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisplayMarkWarning">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bInitiallyLoadAllClips">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bSendNonVisibleBehaviorGraphsToSPU">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMountDismountTimeout">This default value was increased from 5 to 8 with the official 1.6 patch. It is assumed this was necessary because of the introduction of mounted combat.</Description>
    <Description Name="uiMaxNumActorHit">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bCheckRuntimeCollisions">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="bTrackFileLoading">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseArchives">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="iRetainDirectoryStringTable">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="iRetainFilenameOffsetTable">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="iRetainFilenameStringTable">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="sArchiveList">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="sInvalidationFile">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="sResourceArchiveListBeta">This was added with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bLoadBackgroundFaceGen">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseBackgroundFileLoader">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseMultiThreadedTrees">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iPostProcessMillisecondsEditor">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iPostProcessTaskWarningMilliseconds">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxMsUsagePerFrame">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsActiveRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsActorRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsAnimatedObjectsCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsDecalCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsEmittersCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsGeometryCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsHavokTriCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsLightCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsLightExcessGeometry">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsParticlesCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsTriangleCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMsWaterCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uActiveRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uActiveRefCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uActorMemoryBudgetCap">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uActorRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uActorRefCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uAnimatedObjectsCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uAnimatedObjectsCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uCityLODBudgetAdjustment">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uDecalCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uDecalCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uEmittersCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uEmittersCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uGeometryCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uGeometryCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uGeometryMemory">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uGeometryMemoryInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uHavokTriCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uHavokTriCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uLightCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uLightCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uLightExcessGeometry">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uLightExcessGeometryInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uLoadedAreaNonActorMemoryBudgetCap">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uParticlesCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uParticlesCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uRefCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uRefCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uTextureMemory">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uTextureMemoryInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uTriangleCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uTriangleCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uWastelandLODBudgetAdjustment">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uWaterCount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uWaterCountInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uWaterMemory">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uWaterMemoryInterior">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAutoVanityMode">This toggles the vanity camera that spins around the player character after a period of inactivity. Setting this to 1 will disable the vanity camera whereas setting this to 0 will enable it. Changing this on an existing save will have no effect.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDragonCameraTargetPlayer">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReturnTo1stPersonFromVanity">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="f1st3rdSwitchDelay">This sets the maximum transition delay for switching between first and third person views. Setting it to 0 will cause the switch to be instant, but will be extremely close to the character. It is recommended to adjust fMouseWheelZoomSpeed instead.</Description>
    <Description Name="fAutoVanityIncrement">This sets the speed at which the vanity camera spins around the player character with values lower than the default reducing the speed and values higher than the default increasing the speed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fAutoVanityModeDelay">This sets the the time delay in seconds after which the vanity camera that spins around the player character when idle is shown. With the default value, the vanity camera activates when the player character is inactive for 120 seconds.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultAutoVanityZoom">This sets the distance between the vanity camera and player character, with values lower than default zooming in closer to the player character, and values higher than default zooming out farther away from the player character.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDragonCameraDollyTime">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDragonMaxAngleBeforeTurn">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMinCurrentZoom">This sets the minimum zoom in third person mode.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseWheelZoomIncrement">This sets how far zooming with the mouse wheel will go for each turn. It does not expand the zoom range.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseWheelZoomMinDelta">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseWheelZoomSpeed">This sets the transition speed when zooming in and out in third person mode. This also affects how fast the transition from first to third person occurs.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderCombatAddY">This sets the amount of zoom while in combat mode.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderCombatPosX">This sets the the camera position along the x-axis (to the right or to the left) in relation to the player character while in combat mode.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderDragonAddY">This was added with the official 1.8 patch. This sets the amount of zoom while riding a dragon.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderDragonPosX">This was added with the official 1.8 patch. This sets the the camera position along the x-axis (to the right or to the left) in relation to the player character while riding a dragon.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderDragonPosZ">This was added with the official 1.8 patch. This sets the the camera height in relation to the player character while riding a dragon.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderHorseAddY">This sets the amount of zoom while riding a horse.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderHorsePosX">This sets the the camera position along the x-axis (to the right or to the left) in relation to the player character while riding a horse.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderHorsePosZ">This sets the the camera height in relation to the player character while riding a horse.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOverShoulderPosZ">This sets the the camera height in relation to the player character.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVanityModeMaxDistFlyMult">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVanityModeMinDistFly">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bRecord">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sNif">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sOffsetID">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCloudAtlasWidth">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sCloudInstanceMesh">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bChainExplosionDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatAimLocations">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatArea">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatAttackRange">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatCoverReservations">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatDetection">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatGroups2">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatProjectileLOS">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatSearch">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatTargetLocations">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatTargets">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatTextColorDark">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatThreats">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugCombatUnreachableLocations">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableNPCAttacks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDismemberOneLimb">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bHazardDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bIronSightsZoomEnable">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bMagicDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bPlayHitLocationIdles">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bPlayStaggers">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bProjectileDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="f1PBoltTiltUpAngle">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which added Dawnguard compatibility and introduced crossbows.</Description>
    <Description Name="f3PBoltTiltUpAngle">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which added Dawnguard compatibility and introduced crossbows.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDebugCombatProjectileLOSTime">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fDebugCombatTextSize">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fDecapInitialSpeed">This was added with the official 1.2 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fHitVectorDelay">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fIronSightsZoomDefault">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMountedAttackRange">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which introduced mounted combat.</Description>
    <Description Name="fProjectileDebugDuration">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iShowHitVector">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bBackgroundMouse">This toggles the ability of the mouse to move independently inside Skyrim (default where This is disabled) or dependent upon where the cursor actually is in the system (This is enabled). It is recommended to be enabled to prevent awkward mouse behavior during some actions. However, it will probably need to be disabled if windowed mode is used or if the user has multiple monitors.</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowKinectDebugInfo">This was added with the official 1.6 patch. It probably was a debug setting used when fixing some Kinect issues on XBox that were resolved with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDialogueHardStopAngle1P">This controls how far the camera can be rotated while in first-person conversation mode. Expressed in degrees from the original viewport facing. 180 enables full rotation.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDialogueHardStopAngle3P">This controls how far the camera can be rotated while in third-person conversation mode. Expressed in degrees from the player character facing. 180 enables full rotation.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDialogueSoftStopAngle1P">This controls how far the camera can be rotated while in first-person conversation mode before it starts "resisting" further rotation by decreasing the effect the mouse has on the camera. Effectively disabled if set equal to or higher than fDialogueHardStopAngle1P.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDialogueSoftStopAngle3P">This controls how far the camera can be rotated while in third-person conversation mode before it starts "resisting" further rotation by decreasing the effect the mouse has on the camera. Effectively disabled if set equal to or higher than fDialogueHardStopAngle3P.</Description>
    <Description Name="fGamepadHeadingYScale">This default value was increased from 0.5 to 23 in the official 1.2 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMouseHeadingYScale">This default value was increased from 0.01 to 0.8500000238 with the official 1.2 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPCDialogueLookSpeed">This controls how quickly the camera can be rotated/pitched while in conversation mode. Affects both first- and third-person.</Description>
    <Description Name="iNumHotkeys">This default value was increased from 8 to 37 with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="sCopyProtectionMessage2">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sCopyProtectionMessage">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sCopyProtectionTitle2">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sCopyProtectionTitle">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugFaceGenCriticalSection">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugFaceGenMultithreading">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugFlyingMountLeash">This is believed to be unused by the game. This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowDecalsOnAlpha">This toggles decals on what alpha?</Description>
    <Description Name="bBackgroundInitializeGeometryDecals">This toggles the ability of decals on geometry to initialize in the background?</Description>
    <Description Name="bDecalMultithreaded">This is believed to be unused by the game.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDecalOcclusionQuery">This toggles occlusion query on decals?</Description>
    <Description Name="bDecals">This toggles decals.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceAllDecals">This toggles the ability to force all decals to be displayed? If all other decal settings are set to 0, this setting doesn't force them to display, so what does this force? Or does it do nothing?</Description>
    <Description Name="bSkinnedDecals">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fDebrisDecalTimer">This sets how long debris possesses decals?</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxSkinDecalPerActor">This sets the maximum number of skin decals per actor. It is often misspelled uMaxSkinDecalsPerActor and erroneously placed in SkyrimPrefs.ini.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDecals=1Must">This be equal to or less than iMaxSkinDecalsPerFrame (located in SkyrimPrefs.ini in the [Display] section)Must be equal to or less than uMaxSkinDecals.</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxSkinDecals">This sets the maximum number of skin decals. These skin decals are separate from other decals</Description>
    <Description Name="bUse">This Shaders</Description>
    <Description Name="iLocation">This X</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllow20HairShader">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference in the hair was noticed. Since Skyrim requires use of shader model 3.0, it probably is disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllow30Shaders">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed, and it definitely did not turn off shader model 3.0. Since Skyrim requires use of shader model 3.0, it probably is disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowPartialPrecision">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowScreenShot">This toggles the ability to create screenshots in BMP format by pressing the PrintScreen key. Once over three megabytes in size, the files seem to become corrupt.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAutoViewDistance">This toggles a method of automatically determining how far one can see. Unfortunately, the setting is bugged, and causes distant scenery to flash if enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bCompileOnRender">This is believed to be unused by the game. This was likely a debug setting targeting shader compilation during development. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDecalsOnSkinnedGeometry">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDo30VFog">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, setting this to 0 produced identical fog appearance to having it enabled. This does not entirely prove that this setting is unused, but merely shows that it does not affect appearance. It possibly toggles shader model 3.0 for fog, but since Skyrim requires use of shader model 3.0, it probably is disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDoAmbientPass">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDoDiffusePass">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDoSpecularPass">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDoTallGrassEffect">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDoTestHDR">This is believed to be unused by the game. HDR rendering support was dropped in Skyrim. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDoTexturePass">This is believed to be unused by the game. In Oblivion this turned textures off, but in Skyrim it seems to do nothing upon testing.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDynamicWindowReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bEquippedTorchesCastShadows">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bForce1XShaders">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bForceMultiPass">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bForcePow2Textures">This probably was a workaround for graphics cards that cannot use textures that were not powers of 2, forcing all textures to become powers of 2. However, the setting merely causes the game to crash upon loading.</Description>
    <Description Name="bIgnoreResolutionCheck">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bImageSpaceEffects">This toggles imagespace effects, which evidently are necessary, since disabling them induces CTD.</Description>
    <Description Name="bLowHealthIModEnabled">This toggles the blurring effect that occurs when your health is low.</Description>
    <Description Name="bMTRendering">This when enabled does something to the rendering in order to--cause the game to freeze up and not do anything!</Description>
    <Description Name="bReportBadTangentSpace">This is believed to be unused by the game. This was likely a debugging setting for reporting wrong tangents on meshes during development. </Description>
    <Description Name="bShowMarkers">This toggles markers for objects and their bounds like seen in the Creation Kit.</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowMenuTextureUse">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bSimpleLighting">This is a broken setting that causes graphical issues when enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseSunbeams">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fDecalLifetime">This sets the time in seconds that some decals will stay visible.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultFOV">This sets the default field of view in menus, such as the lockpicking interface and inventory.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDefaultWorldFOV">This sets the default field of view of the world, which is what your character sees, in both first and third person.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLightLODDefaultStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change was noticed. It is possible that the value for this setting once changed the default value of fLightLODStartFade, but it does not do that anymore, if it ever did.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLightLODMaxStartFade">This sets the maximum distance that Light Fade (fLightLODStartFade) can be set to in the in-game Settings &gt; Display menu. It appears to have no actual effect.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLightLODMinStartFade">This sets the minimum distance that Light Fade (fLightLODStartFade) can be set to in the in-game Settings &gt; Display menu. It appears to have no actual effect.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLightLODRange">This sets how far away light will fade from the start fade distance (fLightLODStartFade, which is Light Fade in the in-game Settings &gt; Display menu). It is recommended to set it to 50000.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLowHealthIModInterval">This sets the time interval in half seconds of the blurring effect that occurs when your health is low. Setting it to 0 will cause the blur to be constant.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLowHealthIModStrengthMax">This sets the maximum strength of the blurring effect that occurs when your health is low.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLowHealthIModStrengthMin">This sets the minimum strength of the blurring effect that occurs when your health is low.</Description>
    <Description Name="fScopeScissorAmount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowFadeTime">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed. In previous games, this setting set the time in seconds that shadows fade into view, but it appears to be broken in Skyrim.</Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowLODDefaultStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowLODMaxStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowLODMinStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fShadowLODRange">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSkinnedDecalLOD0">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fSpecularLODDefaultStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSpecularLODMaxStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSpecularLODMinStartFade">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSpecularLODRange">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunShadowUpdateTime">This sets the speed of sun-shadow transitions in seconds. Setting this to 0 will cause the transition to be immediate, but jarring.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunUpdateThreshold">This sets the time between sun-shadow transitions. A value of 0.05 is equal to 1 second, so a value of 1 equals 20 seconds. Increasing this also increases the distance the shadows will move during the transition. Setting this to 0 will cause the shadows to constantly be moving outdoors with the sun (not recommended).</Description>
    <Description Name="iAdapter">This sets which screen will display Skyrim in a multi-monitor setup. If it is set incorrectly, it will cause an error saying "Failed to initialize renderer. Bad Adapter Name or Adapter not found."</Description>
    <Description Name="iDebugTextSubPage">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iNPatchNOrder">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iNPatchPOrder">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iPresentInterval">This toggles video synchronization (VSync).</Description>
    <Description Name="iShaderPackageMemoryCap">This sets the maximum amount of memory the shader package is allowed to use. Once this limit has been passed, it will stop displaying objects.</Description>
    <Description Name="sDebugText">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uVideoDeviceIdentifierPart1">This is believed to be unused by the game. It is an Oblivion remnant.</Description>
    <Description Name="uVideoDeviceIdentifierPart2">This is believed to be unused by the game. It is an Oblivion remnant.</Description>
    <Description Name="uVideoDeviceIdentifierPart3">This is believed to be unused by the game. It is an Oblivion remnant.</Description>
    <Description Name="uVideoDeviceIdentifierPart4">This is believed to be unused by the game. It is an Oblivion remnant.</Description>
    <Description Name="sFontConfigFile">This sets the path to the font configuration file.</Description>
    <Description Name="bFootPlacementOn">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bRigidBodyController">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxFootCastMilliSec">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fOriginalGroundHeightMS">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fRagdollFeedback">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowDragonFlightLocationDiscovery">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bHealthBarShowing">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bInstantLevelUp">This is believed to be unused by the game. This appears to be an Oblivion artifact where levelups would not occur until the character slept unless this was enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bTargetLockIsToggle">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bTrackProgress">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fFootIKDistance">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMagicTargetLocationExtraLargeActorRadius">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which introduced Dawnguard compatibility. Therefore, this setting is presumed to be related to vampires in some way.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMagicTargetLocationNormalActorRadius">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which introduced Dawnguard compatibility. Therefore, this setting is presumed to be related to vampires in some way.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerSunGazeDelta">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which introduced Dawnguard compatibility. Therefore, this setting is presumed to be related to vampires' sun allergy.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerSunGazeStartTimer">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which introduced Dawnguard compatibility. Therefore, this setting is presumed to be related to vampires' sun allergy.</Description>
    <Description Name="fTargetLockXYRange">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="iActorsDismemberedPerFrame">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iDetectionPicks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sTrackProgressPath">This is believed to be unused by the game. It appears to be a Fallout 3 artifact.</Description>
    <Description Name="bCreate">This Maps Enable</Description>
    <Description Name="uExterior">This Cell Buffer</Description>
    <Description Name="uInterior">This Cell Buffer</Description>
    <Description Name="bAlwaysActive">This toggles the ability of the game to remain active when it is out of focus (i.e. if in a windowed mode setup, if one clicks outside the Skyrim window with this enabled, the game will not pause).</Description>
    <Description Name="bAnimateDoorPhysics">This may toggle something... but it is uncertain what. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bBackgroundLoadVMData">This toggles the ability of the game to load Papyrus scripting virtual machine data in the background?</Description>
    <Description Name="bBorderRegionsEnabled">This toggles the ability to go outside the borders of a worldspace. It is recommended to be left on.</Description>
    <Description Name="bCRTMemoryChecks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bCalculateArmorMeshAndTextureFileCounts">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bCheckCellOffsetsOnInit">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bCheckPurgedTextureList">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugSpectatorThreats">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAllGore">This toggles the ability of the game to show blood decals and effects.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableDuplicateReferenceCheck">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableGearedUp">This toggles off a bugged feature in Skyrim where all favorite items are shown as equipped and passive on your character. However, if you equip a favorite weapon and them equip another favorite weapon, the first item will become invisible or else become doubly equipped. If the game could be forced to unequip the item before equipping another, this would be a great feature. As is, it is buggy and unuseful except, perhaps, for screen archers.</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableBoundingVolumeOcclusion">This toggles drawing objects that are not directly visible. It is recommended to be left on. </Description>
    <Description Name="bExternalLODDataFiles">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFaceMipMaps">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFlyingMountFastTravelCruiseEnabled">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bKeepPluginWhenMerging">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bParallelAnimUpdate">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bPreCullActors">This toggles drawing actors that are not directly visible. It is recommended to be left on.</Description>
    <Description Name="bRunMiddleLowLevelProcess">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bRunVTuneTest">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bShowCheckMemoryOutput">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bShowGunTarget">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bTaskletActorSceneGraphUpdates">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bTintMipMaps">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseEyeEnvMapping">This is believed to be unused by the game. This may have toggled NPC eye reflections and specular highlights. This worked in Oblivion, but it does not work in Skyrim according to testing.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseMyGamesDirectory">This is believed to be unused by the game. This may have toggled where the game will look for and place the game configuration and load order files. It was an Oblivion tweak, and it seems to have gone to Oblivion, since it does not work in Skyrim according to testing.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseOptimizedTextureLoading">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseThreadedMorpher">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseThreadedParticleSystem">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseThreadedTempEffects">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bWarnOnMissingFileEntry">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fDragonLandingForPlayerNavMeshSize">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDragonLandingForPlayerSearchDist">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fEncumberedReminderTimer">This sets the time interval between subsequent "You are carrying too much to be able to run" messages when the player inventory has exceeded its weight limit.</Description>
    <Description Name="fFlyingMountDismountOffset">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fFlyingMountFastTravelDragonSpeed">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fFlyingMountLandingRequestTimer">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fFlyingMountSlowestSpeedMult">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fFlyingMountTutorialMessageDelay">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMasterFilePreLoadMB">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerFlyingMountBaseTargetSpeed">This was added with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerFlyingMountFastBaseTargetSpeed">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerFlyingMountNothingLoadingMult">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerFlyingMountTravelMaxHeight">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerFlyingMountTravelMinHeight">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="iAIThread1HWThread">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iAIThread2HWThread">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iFPSClamp">This aligns the FPS of gameplay to that of your actual fps. It makes all game actions happen at a speed of your FPS divided by this value. If you get 60 fps and set this to 2, the game animations and everything will be 30 times as fast as normal, with accompanying bugs. If used, it is best to set it at a little under your current FPS. It is recommended to leave this at its default 0 so that the game speed always is the same speed as your FPS.</Description>
    <Description Name="iFlyingMountSlowestQueuedRefCount">This was added with the official 1.8 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread1">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread2">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread3">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread4">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread5">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iHWThread6">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iNumHWThreads">This sets the maximum number of hardware threads the game can use. Set this to the number of cores your CPU has, doubling that number if it has hyperthreading – though setting this to 2 on a DualCore system without hyperthreading may freeze the game.</Description>
    <Description Name="iRenderingThread1HWThread">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iRenderingThread2HWThread">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="sCharGenQuest">This sets the quest id for the starting quest when you begin a new game.</Description>
    <Description Name="sEssentialFileCacheList">This is probably is a caching system for essential game data (game data that is necessary for it to function properly). This should be a list of files with each entry separated by commas. An example value found: Data/Skyrim.esm, Data/Skyrim - Meshes.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Textures.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Animations.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Misc.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Shaders.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Interface.bsa, Data/Skyrim - Sounds.bsa</Description>
    <Description Name="sEssentialFileCacheList=Data/Filename1,">This Data/Filename2, ...</Description>
    <Description Name="sIntroMovie">This is believed to be unused by the game. This may set a movie for whenever a new game is started, playing before the initial quest; however, this only worked for TES IV games.</Description>
    <Description Name="sIntroSequence">This sets the intro sequence movie(s) where by default the Bethesda Logo shows up. Additional movies may be added in sequence using commas. Movies should be locate in Data/Video. Leaving This blank will skip it.</Description>
    <Description Name="sLanguage">This sets the language of the subtitle files to be used. The voice files used are determined upon the language chosen when the game was installed. It is typically in all caps.</Description>
    <Description Name="sLocalMasterPath">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sLocalSavePath">This sets the subdirectory where your game saves are stored at %USERPROFILE%/Documents/My Games/Skyrim. Changing this can be useful if you decide to organize your saves by character or other means. You could rename the save folder with all the John saves in it to John and change this value to access the John saves and so on. This value cannot be changed to a full path. Mod Organizer automatically overrides this setting when using profile-specific saves.</Description>
    <Description Name="sStartingCell">This sets the starting cell for a new game, bypassing the main menu and the main quest startup.</Description>
    <Description Name="sStartingCellX">This sets the x-coordinate in the starting cell specified in sStartingCell.</Description>
    <Description Name="sStartingCellY">This sets the y-coordinate in the starting cell specified in sStartingCell.</Description>
    <Description Name="sStartingWorld">This sets the worldspace of the starting cell specified in sStartingCell.</Description>
    <Description Name="sTestFile1">This through This0 are settings that allow loading of plugins without using the standard loading method. Be advised that plugins loaded here will NOT automatically load their corresponding BSA files if they exist. These, however, can be added to the sArchiveList in [Archive].</Description>
    <Description Name="sUnessentialFileCacheList">This probably is a caching system for unessential game data (game data that is the game can technically run without). This should be a list of files with each entry separated by commas. An example value found: Data/Skyrim - Voices.bsa, Data/Skyrim - VoicesExtra.bsa</Description>
    <Description Name="sUnessentialFileCacheList=Data/Filename1,">This Data/Filename2, ...</Description>
    <Description Name="uGridsToLoad">This sets how much of the world is rendered around the player. The value may only be an odd number that is 5 or higher. Values below 5 will be rounded up to 5. Even numbers shall be rounded up to the higher odd number (e.g., a value of 6 becomes 7). Negative values cause CTD. It is recommended to be left at its default value. Higher values will likely bug out the game over time. </Description>
    <Description Name="fBlockedTexOffset">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fBlurAmmount">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fHitTexOffset">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowCreateGrass">This toggles grass creation. It is an alternative to loading grass (bAllowLoadGrass). It is recommended to be enabled instead of bAllowLoadGrass. The SkyrimLE:Unofficial Skyrim Patch plugin INI contains this setting set to enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowLoadGrass">This toggles grass loading via the grass cache *.gid files. It is an alternative to creating grass (bAllowCreateGrass). It is typically disabled because the grass cache that comes with the vanilla game is not suitable for the current version, as it was never updated correctly by Bethesda. The SkyrimLE:Unofficial Skyrim Patch plugin INI contains this setting set to disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDrawShaderGrass">This toggles the grass shader. Enabling it enables grass, while disabling it will disable grass. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bGenerateGrassDataFiles">This allows the game to create grass cache *.gid files if set to 1. These files can then in turn be loaded via bAllowLoadGrass.</Description>
    <Description Name="bGrassPointLighting">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fGrassDefaultStartFadeDistance">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change was noticed. It is possible that the value for this setting once changed the default value of fGrassStartFadeDistance, but it does not do that anymore, if it ever did.</Description>
    <Description Name="fGrassFadeRange">This sets how far away grass will fade from the start fade distance (fGrassStartFadeDistance, which is Grass Fade in the in-game Settings &gt; Display menu). It is recommended to adjust This rather than increase fGrassStartFadeDistance to reduce grass pop-in effect and performance benefits over the latter.</Description>
    <Description Name="fGrassWindMagnitudeMax">This sets the maximum amount of wind blowing the grass, making the grass move. Setting fGrassWindMagnitudeMin and This to 0 will cause the grass to remain static and may give better performance.</Description>
    <Description Name="fGrassWindMagnitudeMin">This sets the minimum amount of wind blowing the grass, making the grass move. Setting This and fGrassWindMagnitudeMax to 0 will cause the grass to remain static and may give better performance.</Description>
    <Description Name="fTexturePctThreshold">This sets the texture percent threshold of the grass. Valid values range between 0 and 0.2, where 0 is full, and 0.2 altogether removes the grass. Negative values act as 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWaveOffsetRange">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iGrassCellRadius">This sets the radial number of cells that grass is rendered around the player. This must be set to (uGridsToLoad - 1)/2. If set higher, grass will bug out quickly and remove all grass upon walking just a short distance. If set lower, grass will pop into view unrealistically. Negative values disable grass.</Description>
    <Description Name="iMaxGrassTypesPerTexure">This (sic) sets the maximum types of grass per texture. Increasing this will create more diverse kinds of grass, especially with grass mods such as Skyrim Flora Overhaul at a small performance cost. Without grass mods, changing this setting produces little effect. Negative values disable grass. t is recommended to increase this from its default 2 to 3. If using Skyrim Flora Overhaul, it is recommended to set this to 7.</Description>
    <Description Name="iMinGrassSize">This sets the grass density. Lower values produces greater density, but values between 1 and 40 look almost identical. A value of 0 removes all grass. Negative values look almost identical to the values of 1 to 40 but can induce CTDs. High values of around 50 and higher noticeably decrease grass density at a small performance gain. Grass mods such as Grass on Steroids take advantage of this and can create high density grass at high This values. Setting This too high (e.g., 1000) will remove all grass. It is recommended to increase this to at least 40.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAddBipedWhenKeyframed">This toggles the ability of all characters to fly and possess all kinds of funky animations. It is recommended to be left disabled. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDebugMultithreaded">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bHavokDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="bRegisterAllVDBViewers">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bWONameSync">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="fCharControllerWarpDistSqr">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="fJumpAnimDelay">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxPickTimeDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxPickTimeDebugVATS">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="fOD">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fRF">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSD">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSE">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fTimePerSubStep">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="iMinNumSubSteps">This is believed to be unused by the game. It originated with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="iSimType">This changes between different methods of havok behavior? It originated with Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="fHeadTrackingMaxAngle">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bShowInventory3D">This toggles the 3D display of items in the inventory.</Description>
    <Description Name="bShowTutorials">This toggles the in-game tutorial pop-ups. It is recommended to disable them (set to 0) once accustomed to the game.</Description>
    <Description Name="bWriteTranslationFile">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosX">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosXWide">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosY">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosYWide">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosZ">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemPosZWide">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemScale">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCrafting3DItemScaleWide">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fPackratRatio">This default value was changed from 340282346638528860000000000000000000000 to 0 with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="fPlayerRotationAngle">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUILogoModel_AutoRotateSpeed">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUILogoModel_MouseThreshold">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUILogoModel_MouseToPanSpeed">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUILogoModel_RotationPauseDuration">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUILogoModel_ThumbstickToPanSpeed">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUIMistMenu_LogoOnscreenPanThresholdX">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUIMistMenu_LogoOnscreenPanThresholdY">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUIMistMenu_LogoOnscreenZoomThresholdFar">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fUIMistMenu_LogoOnscreenZoomThresholdNear">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sForcedLoadScreenEditorID">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bCurrentCellOnly">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sFailureMessage">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AutoSaveWarning">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AwardsConfiguring">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AwardsInstalling">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AwardsLoading">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AwardsReinstalling">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_AwardsUpdating">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_DirtyDisc">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_DiscEject">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_GameContentInstalling">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_GameDataCorrupt">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_GameDataInsufficientSpace">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_NPDRMInstalling">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_Retry">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_SaveDataCreateNew">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_SaveDataInsufficientSpace">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sSysUtil_SaveDataOwnershipWarning">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fLightEnableDisableFadeTime">This along with the [Light] section was added in the official 1.6 patch, which introduced Dawnguard compatibility. Therefore, it is presumed to be related to the vampires' sun allergy.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDecalLODFadeEnd">This sets the ending fade for decals. It is recommended to be increased.</Description>
    <Description Name="fDistanceMultiplier">This appears to be multiplied against many LOD distance settings.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODLandDropAmount">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODLandVerticalBias">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fLODMultTrees">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fLodDistance">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fTalkingDistance">This sets the distance away from the player that NPCs can move their lips fully while speaking.</Description>
    <Description Name="fAngleMax">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fEyeIKDistanceMax">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxTrackingDist">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMinTrackingDist">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableLipLookup">This was added with the official 1.3 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterHDR">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed; besides, Skyrim does not use HDR rendering. </Description>
    <Description Name="fLowPerfCombatantVoiceDistance">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iDetectionHighNumPicks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iLastHDRSetting">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bWorldMapNoSkyDepthBlur">This toggles off the subtle sky depth blur applied to the map menu. It makes very little difference. It is recommended to be set to 1.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapMenuNearClipPlane">This sets the clipping pane for objects near each other. This effectively helps prevent z-fighting on the map menu. A value of 0 causes extreme z-fighting on the map menu. Unfortunately, it doesn't affect z-fighting elsewhere.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapMenuOverlayScale">This sets the scale of the terrain overlay on the map menu. It is recommended to be very small, but not 0, as 0 looks horrible. The default setting seems to be the best, but experiment with very small values around 0.00009.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapMenuOverlaySnowScale">This sets the scale of the snow overlay on the map menu. It is recommended to be very small, but not 0, as 0 looks horrible.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapWorldMaxPitch">This sets the maximum pitch that the user can change the angle of the map upwards. A value of 90 allows the user to angle the camera perpendicularly to the map while the right mouse button is pressed. A value of 180 will allow the user to look up at the sky overhead. It is recommended to set this to 90.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapWorldMinPitch">This sets the minimum pitch that the user can change the angle of the map downwards. A value of 0 allows the user to angle the camera straight down on the map while the right mouse button is pressed. It is recommended to set this to 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="fMapWorldYawRange">This sets the yaw range that the map menu camera can turn when the right mouse button is pressed. Setting this to 400 allows the user to rotate full circle once. Increasing this beyond 400 allows the user to rotate more than full circle. Obsessively high values (e.g., 3600) induce crashes.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWorldMapDepthBlurScale">This sets the scale of depth blurring applied to the map menu. It is recommended to be set to 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWorldMapMaximumDepthBlur">This sets the maximum amount of depth blurring applied to the map menu. It is recommended to be set to 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWorldMapNearDepthBlurScale">This sets the amount of depth blurring applied to the map menu at higher elevations. It is recommended to be set to 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="uLockedObjectMapLOD">This sets the level of detail of objects on the map menu. Lowering this produces better details on objects, especially river falls, but will cause the map to load slightly slower. It has been observed to sometimes cause infinite loading screens when loading saves where it was a higher value. It is recommended to set this to 8.</Description>
    <Description Name="uLockedTerrainLOD">This sets the level of detail of the terrain on the map menu. Lowering this produces better details on terrain, but will cause the map to load significantly slower (as in, wait thirty seconds for the map to load). It is therefore NOT recommended to lower this.</Description>
    <Description Name="iConsoleHistoryCharBufferSize">This sets the number of characters that are displayed in the history list when using console commands like help. The default setting shows the last 16,384 characters in the history list.</Description>
    <Description Name="iConsoleSizeScreenPercent">This sets the vertical size of the console as a percentage of vertical screen resolution. The default of 40 means the console occupies the lower 40 percent (or slightly less than half) of the vertical space. Note that MFG Console uses the available screen space above the debug console, so increasing the size of the debug console may force MFG Console to use a smaller font to make everything fit in the available space.</Description>
    <Description Name="iConsoleTextSize">This sets the size of the font in the console.</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowFileWrite">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAssertQueuing">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFaceGenWarnings">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWindowsMessageBox">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableLogging">This toggles Papyrus logs being written to disk. It is recommended to be disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableProfiling">This toggles script profiling, which enables profiling commands and allows profiling information to be logged, at the cost of some script performance. It is recommended to be disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableTrace">This toggles script tracing. Trace commands will not display in-game if this is disabled. It is recommended to be disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bLoadDebugInformation">This toggles additional debug information. If enabled, line number information will be available in error traces at the expense of higher memory usage. It is recommended to be disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="uTraceStatusOfQuest">This sets a quest to track for script changes by form ID (converted to decimal). If Papyrus logging is enabled, every time a Papyrus script tries to change something with the quest that this setting specifies, like starting, stopping, setting a stage, or showing an objective, it will log the Papyrus stack trace. It was added with the official 1.6 patch.</Description>
    <Description Name="bRebuildPathIfSmootherFailed">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bSlowDownForActorAvoidance">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseAlternateSmoothingForPrime">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseOldPathSmoothing">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUsePathSmoothing">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseTaskletsToRecomputeBounds">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bWarnIfHighLevelSearchFails">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fAICombatTurnSpeedScale">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fAITurnSpeedScale">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMaxDistanceMoved">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMinDist">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fMinTimeToNextPoint">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fObstacleUpdateDeltaWhenUnknown">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fPOVSmootherAvoidNodeCost">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fPathManagerDebugInfoWindow">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="iMaxPathRequestsPerFrameTracked">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bLookIK">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bRagdollFeedback">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fCameraDist">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fFeedbackImpulseMult">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="uiFeedbackTimeout">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowProfileTransfer">This is believed to be unused by the game.  Interestingly, Google found the following comment about it: ";This should be set to 0 or removed when we ship."</Description>
    <Description Name="bAllowScriptedAutosave">This toggles scripted autosaves.</Description>
    <Description Name="bCopySaveGameToHostOrMemStick">This probably is a console setting. It is unknown to do anything on the PC version.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisableAutoSave">This toggles off autosaves. If set to 1, all autosaves will be disabled, even if left on in the other relevant INI settings.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisplayMissingContentDialogue">This toggles the dialogue box that appears when a save is attempted to be loaded when one or more plugins previously used on that save have been removed from the load order.</Description>
    <Description Name="bOutputSaveGameScreenshot">This is believed to be unused by the game. This setting, although introduced in Skyrim, appears to do nothing. The title suggests that it would output a screenshot when a game is saved, but no screenshot was observed, and it does not change the built-in screenshot in the save.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUsePagedBuffers">This was added in the official patch 1.4. Since the 1.4 changelog says it "Fixed rare crash with loading saved games," this addition most likely is the fix for said issue. Therefore, it is recommended to remain enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseSaveGameHistory">This is a mystery setting. It is currently unknown what it might do.</Description>
    <Description Name="iAutoSaveCount">This sets the maximum amount of autosaves allowed before removing the oldest autosave.</Description>
    <Description Name="iSaveGameBackupCount">This sets the number of backup save files with a .bak file extension to save. Each additional backup will have a extra .bak added to the end of it (e.g., if set to 2, there will be two backups for autosave1.ess: autosave1.ess.bak and autosave1.ess.bak.bak). Note that these backups are not identical, which leaves reason to believe that either each backup is generated independently of the original save, or there is some bug in the backup mechanism. Setting this to 0 will create no backups.</Description>
    <Description Name="sSaveGameGameVersionOutdated">This was moved from the [MAIN] section to the [SaveGame] section with the official 1.2 patch. This message is displayed if a savegame from a newer version of Skyrim is attempted to be loaded on an older version of Skyrim. Currently, any savegame created on the latest version of Skyrim (1.9.32.0.8) will display this warning if attempted to be played on a version below 1.6.</Description>
    <Description Name="sSaveGameSafeMarkerID">This is a mystery setting. It is currently unknown what it might do.</Description>
    <Description Name="bBloodSplatterEnabled">This toggles screen blood splatter. Unfortunately, disabling it also causes the map menu to CTD.</Description>
    <Description Name="fLODSnowThresholdAngle">This sets the snow level of detail threshold angle on distant terrain and the map menu (i.e., the amount of snow layered on distant mountains). It does not help z-fighting on distant mountains.</Description>
    <Description Name="bDisplayCloudLOD">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bKeepLowDetailTerrain">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bUseNewTerrainSystem">This toggles the new terrain system. Disabling this will go back to the Oblivion terrain system where terrain fades into view as you approach it rather than getting more detailed as you approach it.</Description>
    <Description Name="uDistantTreeBlockCacheSizePerCell">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileCheckModelCollision">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileControllerOnRoot">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileGoneMessage">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileNeededMessage">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileShowIcons">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileShowTextures">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileSkipIconChecks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileSkipModelChecks">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileTestLoad">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bFileUnusedObject">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableTreeAnimations">This toggles the "dynamic" rendering of trees. If disabled, all trees will be skinned and inanimate, using the "static" version of tree rendering. It seems to do the same thing as bEnableTrees. See the Skyrim Tree Settings Guide for more information.</Description>
    <Description Name="bEnableTrees">This toggles the "dynamic" rendering of trees. If disabled, all trees will be skinned and inanimate, using the "static" version of tree rendering. It seems to do the same thing as bEnableTreeAnimations. See the Skyrim Tree Settings Guide for more information.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceFullDetail">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing with multiple different combinations, no difference was noticed.This setting originated with Oblivion, where it forced full tree LOD to display. Since both games use completely different tree systems, it most likely has no effect.</Description>
    <Description Name="bPickSkinnedTrees">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing with multiple different combinations, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fUpdateBudget">This appears to control the amount of resources allocated to tree animations. If set to 0, tree animations will be effectively disabled while not causing all trees to be skinned. See the Skyrim Tree Settings Guide for more information.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSAllowNoKill">This toggles the camera animation that zooms in on the target NPC when attacked but not killed. This enables the "kill cam" effect even when the target NPC is not hit or killed. Set this to 0 disable or 1 to enable the camera animation when attacking NPCs. This was added with the official 1.5 patch. Since the changelog states that it added "New cinematic kill cameras for projectile weapons and spells," this setting is presumed to be associated with that.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSDisable">This toggles the camera animation that zooms in on the target NPC when killed. Set this to 0 to enable or 1 to disable the camera animation when the target NPC is killed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSForceRanged">This was added with the official 1.5 patch. Since the changelog states that it added "New cinematic kill cameras for projectile weapons and spells," this setting is presumed to be associated with that.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSIgnoreProjectileTest">This was added with the official 1.5 patch. Since the changelog states that it added "New cinematic kill cameras for projectile weapons and spells," this setting is presumed to be associated with that.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSMultipleCombatants">This toggles the camera animation that zooms in on the target NPC when attacked or killed and multiple combatants are present. Set this to 0 to disable or 1 to enable the camera animation when multiple combatants are present. This was added with the official 1.5 patch. Since the changelog states that it added "New cinematic kill cameras for projectile weapons and spells," this setting is presumed to be associated with that.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSRangedSelective">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="bVATSSmartCameraCheckDebug">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSCastingAfterKillDelay">This was added with the official 1.5 patch. Since the changelog states that it added "New cinematic kill cameras for projectile weapons and spells," this setting is presumed to be associated with that.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSFocus">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangedLongDistance">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangedLowHealthPercent">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangedPercentMin">This sets the minimum percentage the camera zoom effect is shown in ranged attacks when not sneaking. The default value of 50 means the camera zoom effect is shown in 50% of attacks that kill the target NPC. This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATARangedPercentSneakKills">This sets the percentage the camera zoom effect is shown in ranged attacks when sneaking. The default value of 20 means the camera zoom effect is shown in 20% of attacks that kill the target NPC. fVATSRangedPercentSneakKill was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangePercentTargetNoThreat">This sets the percentage the camera zoom effect is shown in ranged attacks when the target NPC is not a threat. fVATSRangedPercentTargetNoThreat was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="fVATSRangedTargetLowLevelMult">This was added with the official 1.6 patch, which refined the logic of kill moves, resolving a number of issues.</Description>
    <Description Name="sFileTypeGame">This is believed to be unused by the game. It probably would set the filetype for voice files, default being wav files. In previous game, other types like mp3 have been used. Setting it to mp3 does not remove voices.</Description>
    <Description Name="sFileTypeLTF">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sFileTypeLip">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sFileTypeSource">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="bAutoWaterSilhouetteReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed. This setting originates with Fallout 3.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceHighDetailReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.In Fallout 3, this forced more objects to be reflected in the water.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceLowDetailReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bForceLowDetailWater">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectExplosions">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, it was found that a firebolt was reflected across the water regardless of this setting.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectLODLand">This toggles land reflections in the water. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectLODObjects">This toggles object reflections in the water. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectLODTrees">This toggles tree reflections in the water. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bReflectSky">This toggles sky reflections in the water. It can appear buggy sometimes when you move the camera, so it is recommended to be disabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseBulletWaterDisplacements">This is believed to be unused by the game. Arrows were shot into the water, but no displacement occurred. It is therefore believed that there is no "bullet water displacement" available in the game.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseCubeMapReflections">This toggles cube map reflections, and much more! Disabling this will effectively make water invisible unless the player is swimming underneath it. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUsePerWorldSpaceWaterNoise">This toggles water noise. It is recommended to be enabled.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWater">This toggles water visibility. Disabling this will remove all water from view, but it can still be swam through. It can also induce CTD.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterHiRes">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterLOD">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterReflectionBlur">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="bUseWaterShader">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fCubeMapRefreshRate">This sets the refresh rate of cube map reflections in seconds. If set to 60, water reflections will be calculated only once every minute. This will cause the reflections not to show for the first minute, after which they will pop into place. It is recommended to leave this at 0 so that reflections are calculated in realtime.</Description>
    <Description Name="fExteriorWaterReflectionThreshold">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fInteriorWaterReflectionThreshold">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fRefractionWaterPlaneBias">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSurfaceTileSize">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fTileTextureDivisor">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWadingWaterQuadSize">This sets the size of the displacement of water created when wading through water. It is recommended to be left at its default value.</Description>    
    <Description Name="fWadingWaterTextureRes">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fWaterGroupHeightRange">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iWaterBlurAmount">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="iWaterNoiseResolution">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="sSurfaceTexture">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change was observed when a random string was entered. This appears to be a remnant from Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxExteriorWaterReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, setting this to 0 did not disable water reflections outdoors.</Description>
    <Description Name="uMaxInteriorWaterReflections">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, setting this to 0 did not disable water reflections indoors.</Description>
    <Description Name="uSurfaceFPS">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no change in the smoothness of the water was observed. This appears to be a remnant from Oblivion.</Description>
    <Description Name="bFogEnabled">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, it did not disable fog when set to 0.</Description>
    <Description Name="bPrecipitation">This toggles precipitation. Setting it to 0 will disable all rain and snow.</Description>
    <Description Name="fAlphaReduce">This is believed to be unused by the game. In testing, no difference was noticed.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunBaseSize">This sets the sun base size. Setting it to 0 will remove the sun altogether, albeit the day will still be lit. Negative values have the same effect as positive values.</Description>
    <Description Name="fSunGlareSize">This sets the amount of sun glare. Setting this to 0 will not disable sun glare, and negative values act the same as positive values. Extremely high values will cause a glare line.</Description>
    <Description Name="sBumpFadeColor">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sEnvReduceColor">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
    <Description Name="sLerpCloseColor">This is believed to be unused by the game. </Description>
  </Descriptions>
</Bethesda>
